



Hello, I'm Gwen.

775.342.9991 gwenewasko@gmail.com

ට 🕀 🔰 @gwen

Here's My Story

My name is Gwen Ewasko, I have been a graphic designer for the better part of 10 years. Born in Seattle, and raised on the Nevada side of Lake Tahoe.

My experience ranges from agency work to in-house. Finding and building a brand's story is my passion. Creating beautiful and purposeful design is my mission.

Education

Everett Community College Associates of Fine Arts Visual Communication

Work Experience

Tahoe Mountain Realty
Creative Director
June 2017 - present

Extra-Curricular

AIGA Reno/Tahoe Board Member 2013 - 2015

AIGA Reno/Tahoe Mentor 2014

My Role:

- Manage creative brand assets
- Strategize and execute on-brand collateral for digital and traditional media
- Copywriting

Reno Wired 2013 and 2014

With a skilled team of designers, writers and developers, I helped re-brand a non-profit in 24 hours.

- Manage social media for 3 separate brands
- Regular website updates (Wordpress)
- Event planning
- Vendor Management

Freelance Designer Aug. 2016 - July 2017

- Production work for local designer and mentor, Kelly Wallis.
- Apparel, print and digital design work for Tahoe University (clothing store).

KPS3 Marketing
Graphic Designer
Sept. 2012 - Aug. 2016

- Creative brand development from concept to execution
- Brand management across digital and traditional mediums
- Production work
- Video editing
- Art direction

Everett Community College Graphic Designer June 2010 - July 2012

- Designing original posters and marketing for on-campus events
- Creating event assets for social media and digital spaces
- Serving as event photographer

